Guide to the Lessons of the Sixties: A history of local Washington, DC activism for peace and justice from 1960-1975:Personal papers, 1937-2016, bulk 1967-1981 MS2392
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Alice Wolfson papers, Circa 1970-1980; Series 12
  - DC Liberation papers, Circa 1970; Series 12 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Women's health issues, Circa 1968-1978; Series 12 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Lesbianism, 1969; Series 12 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Pill hearings, 1970; Series 12 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Abortion, Circa 1969; Series 12 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Scarf and picture of Alice Wolfson, 1969; Series 12 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - SNCC Black Women's liberation, undated; Series 12 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Women A Journal of Liberation, 1970; Series 12 (Box 14, Folder 15)
- Malcolm Davis papers, Circa 1970-1976; Series 13
  Biography
  Malcolm Davis (1937-2011) - was an Ecumenical campus chaplain at George Washington University (GWU) from 1967 until 1984. Throughout the late 1960s-early 1970s, Davis's campus office served as a gathering and planning spot for civil rights and antiwar activists. Davis personally fought for social justice -- in the South organizing civil rights bus caravans and sit-ins, leading voter registration drives, confronting the Ku Klux Klan; in D.C. helping organize the Poor People's Campaign and its accompanying Resurrection City in 1968, and helping organize anti-war protests during the Vietnam War. He later became renowned for his porcelain pottery. Panel participants, all of whom were student activists at George Washington during the late 1960s and early 1970s, were: Sally Benbasset Tim Frasca Lexi Freeman Richard Lipsitz Esther Siegel George Virkus.
  This series contains documents and newspaper clippings that cover the part of Malcolm Davis' campus ministry at GWU, in the People's Union.The materials date from the early to middle 1970s.
  For the Lessons of the Sixties oral history project, Malcolm Davis was remembered by Sally Benbasset, Tim Frasca, Lexi Freeman, Richard Lipsitz, Esther Siegel, and George Virkus. All of whom were student activists at George Washington during the late 1960s and early 1970s. The interview titled "Malcolm Davis Remembered" is part of collection MS2388. Listen to the interview.
  - People's Union Notebook, 1970-1972; MS2392 Series 13 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    Keywords provided by the donor: People's Union,George Washington University, eviction, protest, GW master plan.
  - GWU, 1965-2011; MS2392 Series 13 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    Keywords provided by the donor: GW, GWU, People's Union, letters, statements, reports, fliers, Poor People's Campaign, United Campus Christian Ministry, National Campus Ministry Association (NCMA), United Christian Fellowship, socialism.
  - Anti-war movement, Circa 1970-1972; MS2392 Series 13 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    Keywords provided by the donor: ROTC, Abolish ROTC, Draft, C.S.A., Community Student Alliance, university research.
- Larry Aaronson draft of memoir, 2017-2018; Series 14
  Larry Aaronson was a participant in the Lessons of the Sixties oral history project. The interview is part of collection MS2388. Listen to the interview..
  Larry Aaronson grew up in Washington DC, where he began a teaching career after college. He cut his political teeth in the local civil rights movement, moving later to Cambridge, MA to teach in public schools for over forty years. Larry maintains that he has learned more from his hundreds of students than they ever learned from him.
  - First draft of memoir, 2017-2018; MS2392 Series 14 (Box 15, Folder 8)